Guide to the Peabody Museum of Natural History, Yale University, Botanical Teaching Slides
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Glass Slides, Accession 1989-A-042
  - II. Principles
    - C - Plant Succession
      - 3 - Succession on Rock
        - Isle Royale, Michigan, 1909, 1932 (Box 90)
        - Deer Park Canon, 1911 (Box 90)
      - 4 - Successions on Sand
        - Bryants Hardwoods, 1919, 1921, 1922, 1923, 1933 (Box 91)
        - Lake Michigan Sand Dunes (Box 91)
        - Millers, Ind., 1911, 1933, 1910 (Box 91)
        - Sturgeon Bay, Michigan, 1931 (Box 91)
        - Dune Park, Ind., 1897, 1905, 1912, 1902, 1899, 1900 (Box 91)
        - Lake Michigan Sand Dunes (Box 92)
        - Sleeping Bear Point, Mich., 1932, 1915 (Box 92)
        - Gary, Ind., 1909, 1933 (Box 92)
        - California Dunes (Box 93)
        - Monterey, 1919, 1920, 1922, 1923, 1927 (Box 93)
        - Gulf Coast Dunes (Box 93)
        - Florida Dunes (Box 93)
        - Cape Cod Dunes
          See: Succession on Sand-Connecticut
      - 5 - Successions on River Bars, Flood Plains, Mud Flats
        - Marion, N. C., 1916 (Box 93)
        - Missouri River flats, 1927, 1928, 1929 (Box 93)
        - Missouri River flats, 1930 (Box 94)
        - Manhattan, Kansas, 1924, 1926, 1931 (Box 94)
        - Utica, III., 1910 (Box 94)
        - Saline Areas (Box 94)
        - Sand Plains (Box 94)
        - Nebraska Sandhills, 1912 (Box 94)
      - 6 - Successions on Salt Marshes (Box 95)
      - 7 - Succession on Bogs
        - Peat Excavation in Cambridge, 1935
          See: Succession on Bogs-Connecticut
        - Lakes and Marshes (Box 95)
      - 8 - Erosion Effects
        - Thorn Creek, 1911 (Box 96)
        - Marion, N. C., 1916 (Box 96)
    - D - Aggregation - Migration - Ecesis (lacking)
      - 1 - Aggregation (lacking) (Box 96)
      - 2 - Migration Methods (lacking) (Box 96)
      - 3 - Direction of Migration (lacking) (Box 96)
      - 4 - Ecesis (lacking) (Box 96)
    - E - Competition and Invasion
      - 1 - Competition/ Plant Competition (Box 96)
    - 2 - Invasion
      - Northwest Nebraska, 1912 (Box 96)
      - Aikman succession series, 1930 (Box 96)
    - F - Factors of Habitat
      - 1 - Soil (Box 96)
      - 1 - Soil (Box 97)
      - 2 - Precipitation (Box 97)
    - G - Relation of Underground Plant Parts to Environment
      - 1 - Humidity (Box 97)
      - 2 - Wind Effects
        - New York Times Magazine Section, 1927 (Box 98)
        - West-central Kansas, 1935 (Box 98)
        - Yale National Reserve, 1939 (Box 98)
      - 3 - Temperature Influence (Box 98)
      - 4 - Light Effects (Box 98)
      - 4 - Light Effects
        - Photoperodism, 1920, 1923, 1932 (Box 99)
        - Lightning (Box 99)
        - Catskills, 1904 (Box 99)
      - 5 - Relationships between Plants and Animals
        - Russia, 1927 (Box 99)
        - Douglas Lake, Michigan, 1932, 1925, 1929 (Box 99)
        - Beaver pond, 1927 (Box 99)
        - Photos by Norman McClintock (Box 99)
        - Salisbury, 1915 (Box 100)
        - Lower Michigan, early, 1880s (Box 100)
        - Effects of grazing, 1930, 1927 (Box 100)
        - Columbia National Forest, Oregon (Box 100)
        - Payette National Forest, Utah, 1014, 1931 (Box 100)
        - Mantic National Forest, Utah, 1914, 1925 (Box 100)
        - Vegetation Maps (Box 100)
        - Vegetation Maps (Box 101)
        - Glaciers (Box 101)
        - Maps (Box 101)
      - 6 - Pollination (lacking) (Box 101)
  - III - Climax Formations
    - A - Tundra Climax
      See: Alaska Travel series
    - B - Forest Climaxes
      See: Dendrology File, No.D73G
      - Nichols, 1935 (Box 102)
      - 1 - The Boreal Forest (Box 102)
      - 2 - Sub- Alpine Forest (Box 102)
      - 3 - South Eastern Coastal Forests
        - New Jersey, 1932, 1930, 1933 (Box 102)
        - Auburn, Alabama, 1930 (Box 102)
      - 4 - The Montane Forest
        - Olympic Peninsula Forests (Box 103)
      - 5 - The Deciduous Forest (Box 103)
      - 6 - 1 - True Prairie
        - Western Nebraska, 1912, 1914 (Box 104)
        - Great Plains, 1917 (Box 104)
      - 6 - 1 - (cont'd) (Box 105)
      - 6 - 2 - Sub-Climax Prairie (Box 105)
      - 6 - 3 - Coastal Prairie/ South Carolina Coastal Plain (Box 105)
      - 6 - 4 - Chaparral Climax
        - Macchia - Corsica (Box 105)
        - Chaparral Burn Regeneration (Box 105)
        - Santa Lucia Mts., Calif., 1913, 1914, 1915, 1918, 1920, 1922 (Box 105)
      - 6 - 5 - Sagebrush Climax
        - So. Nevada - Las Vegas (Box 106)
        - Tooele, Utah (Box 106)
        - Texas Scrub (Box 107)
        - Edwards Plateau (Box 107)
      - 6 - 6 - Desert-Scrub Climax
        - Map of Western U.S., 1852 (Box 107)
        - Death Valley (Box 107)
      - 6 - 6 - (cont'd)
        - Agave: Washington Park, Chicago, 1907 (Box 108)
        - Yucca
          - So. Nevada (Box 108)
          - Mohave desert (Box 108)
          - Palm Springs, Calif. (Box 108)
          - Arizona (Box 108)
          - New Mexico (Box 108)
        - Yucca (Box 109)
        - Dasylirion: Arizona (Box 109)
        - Cacti
          - Arizona (Box 109)
          - Tucson, 1928, 1906 (Box 109)
          - Santa Catalina Mts. (Box 109)
        - Cereus: Arizona (Box 110)
        - Echinocactus: Arizona (Box 110)
        - Machaerocerus: Santa Domingo, Baja, Calif. (Box 110)
        - Opuntia (Cholla)
          - Arizona (Box 110)
          - Desert near Tucson (Box 110)
        - Organ Pipe Cactus: Arizona (Box 110)
        - Fouquiera: Arizona (Box 110)
        - Seasonal Changes in Vegetation
          - Tucson, March and, October, 1932 (Box 111)
          - Columbia, Mo., various monthly aspects (Box 111)
  - Tropic Vegetation: Philippine Islands (Box 111)
  - Morphology
    - Specialized Cells and Organs (Box 112)
    - Plant Organs and Meristems (Box 112)
      Slide No. M14C is cracked.
  - Morphology and Anatomy
    - New Haven, 1931 (Box 113)
    - 1915 (Box 113)
    - Palynology (Box 113)
    - Root Nodules (Box 113)
    - Rhizomes (Box 114)
    - Roots: Shark River, Florida, 1937 (Box 114)
    - Roots (Box 115)
  - Thallophytes
    - Algae: Phaeophyceae (Box 115)
    - Lichens (Box 115)
  - Bryophyta
    - Mosses
      - Bryales (Box 115)
      - Sphagnales
        - New York Botanical Garden, 1918 (Box 116)
        - Sphagnum Moss Series (Box 116)
        - Sphagnum Moss Series (cont'd) (Box 117)
  - Anthocerotales (Box 117)
  - Marchanteales (Box 117)
  - Jungermanniales Anacrogynae (Box 118)
  - Jungermanniales Acrogynae
    - Hepaticae (Box 118)
    - Hepaticae (cont'd) (Box 119)
  - Psilophytales: Paleo Botany, Quinnipiac River, 1912
  - Equisetales: Equisetum (Box 120)
  - Lycopodiales (Box 120)
  - Pteridophyta
    - Filicales (Box 120)
    - Cycads: Chavarrillo, Mexico, 1906 (Box 121)
    - Gnetophytes:- South Africa (Box 121)
    - Ginkgo (Box 121)
    - Dispersal (Box 121)
    - Parasites (Box 121)
  - Botanists, Botanical Gatherings, etc.
    - Staten Island, 1915 (Box 122)
    - Santa Catalina Mts., Arizona, 1913 (Box 122)
    - Berlin, 1924 (Box 122)
  - Miscellaneous slides (Box 123–125)